Ellen L. Lutz Papers MS177
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
- Publications, presentations and conference files, 1942 -- 2009; 1985 -- 2008; MS177.010; 10.8 Linear Feet; 5 Digital Object(s)
  - Democracy - General: Elections, 1992 -- 1994; MS177.010.013.00012 (Box 13)
  - Democracy - General: Fox, Nolte 'Intolerant Democracies', 1995; MS177.010.013.00013 (Box 13)
  - Democracy - General [1 of 3], 1992 -- 1996; MS177.010.013.00014 (Box 13)
  - Democracy - General [2 of 3], 1992 -- 1996; MS177.010.013.00015 (Box 13)
  - Democracy - General [3 of 3], 1989 -- 1995; MS177.010.013.00016 (Box 13)
  - Democracy - Latin America: ASIL / IIJ EL conf. paper [1 of 2], 1991 -- 1996; MS177.010.013.00017 (Box 13)
  - Democracy - Latin America: ASIL / IIJ EL conf. paper [2 of 2], 1994 -- 1996; MS177.010.013.00018 (Box 13)
  - Democracy - Latin America: [Convergence and Community: The Americas in 1993], MS177.010.013.00019 (Box 13)
  - Democracy - Latin America: [Sovereignty and Democracy: Authors' Working Group Session, 1 of 2], 1993; MS177.010.013.00020 (Box 13)
  - Democracy - Latin America: [Sovereignty and Democracy: Authors' Working Group Session, 2 of 2], 1993; MS177.010.013.00021 (Box 13)
  - Democracy - Latin America, 1994; MS177.010.013.00022 (Box 13)
  - OAS - post 1945 developments re: democracy - documents, 1994 -- 1997; MS177.010.013.00023 (Box 13)
  - UU sermon 3/96, 1996; MS177.010.013.00024 (Box 13)
  - Bosnia tribunal debate, Rubin / Scharf 5/96, 1996; MS177.010.013.00025 (Box 13)
  - ACUNS conf., 1996; MS177.010.013.00026 (Box 13)
  - NGO paper for ACUNS conf. and materials for article 6/96, 1996; MS177.010.013.00027 (Box 13)
  - EPIIC talk and exercise, 1996; MS177.010.013.00028 (Box 13)
  - [Women in international law talk], 1996; MS177.010.013.00029 (Box 13)
  - [Women in international law talk] UN / Women, Beijing and Beyond and women at UN, 1995 -- 1996; MS177.010.013.00030 (Box 13)
  - EPIIC symposium talk 4/97, 1997; MS177.010.013.00031 (Box 13)
  - [Visions and Frictions in the Information Age, Harvard tech conference talk], 1997; MS177.010.013.00032 (Box 13)
  - Whittier College talk - 4/97, 1997; MS177.010.014.00001 (Box 14)
  - HR talk, health and H.R. - Harvard, 1997; MS177.010.014.00002 (Box 14)
  - EL - misc. recent work, 1997 -- 1999; MS177.010.014.00003 (Box 14)
  - [Enforcement of the International Prohibition Against Torture and Other Cruel, Inhuman or Degrading Treatment or Punishment, draft], 1997; MS177.010.014.00006 (Box 14)
  - [1998: 'Responses to Amnesties by the Inter-American System for the Protection of Human Rights'] D. Harris - Oxford book, chap. re: amnesty, 1996; MS177.010.014.00007 (Box 14)
  - [1998: 'Responses to Amnesties by the Inter-American System for the Protection of Human Rights,' draft], 1997; MS177.010.014.00008 (Box 14)
  - Impunity / Amnesty / Truth commissions, 1994; MS177.010.014.00010 (Box 14)
  - Impunity / Amnesty / Truth commissions - Orentlicher, 'Settling Accounts,' Nino, response, 1991; MS177.010.014.00011 (Box 14)
  - Impunity / Amnesty / Truth commissions - Amnesty - Latin America, 1989 -- 1995; MS177.010.014.00012 (Box 14)
  - Impunity / Amnesty / Truth commissions - IAHCR rpts re: amnesties (Argentina, Uruguay, El Salvador), 1992 -- 1996; MS177.010.014.00013 (Box 14)
  - Impunity / Amnesty / Truth commissions - Impunity / Latin America, 1991 -- 1993; MS177.010.014.00014 (Box 14)
  - Impunity / Amnesty / Truth commissions - Truth Commissions, 1994 -- 1995; MS177.010.014.00015 (Box 14)
  - Haiti, 1995 -- 1997; MS177.010.014.00016 (Box 14)
  - Chili [1 of 2], 1994 -- 1996; MS177.010.014.00017 (Box 14)
  - Chili [2 of 2], 1991 -- 1995; MS177.010.014.00018 (Box 14)
  - Peru, 1995 -- 1996; MS177.010.014.00019 (Box 14)
  - Guatemala, 1995 -- 1997; MS177.010.014.00020 (Box 14)
  - Uruguay, 1989 -- 1991; MS177.010.014.00021 (Box 14)
  - Nicaragua, 1988; MS177.010.014.00022 (Box 14)
  - [AAAS conference], 1999; MS177.010.014.00023 (Box 14)
  - JDL/BCC talk 4/15/99, 1999; MS177.010.014.00024 (Box 14)
  - Tufts: Latin America and Rule of Law conference '99, 1999; MS177.010.014.00025 (Box 14)
  - Grolier contract, 1999; MS177.010.014.00026 (Box 14)
  - International Criminal Court - 400 words, 1998 -- 1999; MS177.010.014.00027 (Box 14)
  - Genocide - 750 words, 1999; MS177.010.014.00028 (Box 14)
  - War Crimes - 5000 words, 1999; MS177.010.014.00029 (Box 14)
  - Grolier - final articles, 1999; MS177.010.014.00030 (Box 14)
  - EL articles, 1999 -- 2003; MS177.010.014.00031 (Box 14)
  - [SPIDR / CRENET conference: Opening the Way to a Civil Society: Creating a Culture of Community and Dialogue], 2000; MS177.010.014.00032 (Box 14)
  - PICAR conference notes, 2000; MS177.010.014.00033 (Box 14)
  - Lecture on Mexico for Hannum's H.R. law course, 2000 -- 2001; MS177.010.014.00034 (Box 14)
  - NE SPIDR conference proposal, 2000; MS177.010.014.00035 (Box 14)
  - [SPIDR panel: Human Rights and Conflict Resolution], 2000; MS177.010.014.00036 (Box 14)
  - AIUSA HR Day talk, 2000; MS177.010.014.00037 (Box 14)
  - Transparency International, 2000; MS177.010.014.00038 (Box 14)
  - Op ed re: bringing Milosevic to justice, 2000; MS177.010.014.00039 (Box 14)
  - [2000: 'International Human Rights Law and Practice in Latin America'] E. Lutz / K. Sikkink paper for IO Journal, 1997 -- 1999; MS177.010.014.00040 (Box 14)
  - [2000: 'International Human Rights Law and Practice in Latin America'] IO articles - preliminary papers, Legalization and World Politics [1 of 2], 1998 -- 1999; MS177.010.014.00041 (Box 14)
  - [2000: 'International Human Rights Law and Practice in Latin America'] IO articles - preliminary papers, Legalization and World Politics [2 of 2], 1998 -- 1999; MS177.010.014.00042 (Box 14)
  - [2000: 'International Human Rights Law and Practice in Latin America' in International Organization], MS177.010.014.00043 (Box 14)
  - K. Sikkink grant proposal / 00, 2000; MS177.010.015.00001 (Box 15)
  - Comparative charts, 1998 -- 1999; MS177.010.015.00002 (Box 15)
  - Latin American ratification of human rights treaties, 1999; MS177.010.015.00003 (Box 15)
  - Latin American support for ICC, 1998; MS177.010.015.00004 (Box 15)
  - [Untitled essay on Brazil trip], 2000; MS177.010.015.00005 (Box 15)
  - M. Gopin - Talk on reconciliation, 2/01, 2001; MS177.010.015.00006 (Box 15)
  - A. Bartolli talk, 2001; MS177.010.015.00007 (Box 15)
  - Pinochet precedent conference A.U., 2001; MS177.010.015.00008 (Box 15)
  - Susan Opotow 4/23/01 PICAR, Psychology of Injustice, 2001; MS177.010.015.00009 (Box 15)
  - N. Soderberg talk, 2001; MS177.010.015.00010 (Box 15)
  - Conflict resolution perspectives on events post 9/11, 12/4/01, 2001; MS177.010.015.00011 (Box 15)
  - Mexico talk, 2001; MS177.010.015.00012 (Box 15)
  - [2001: 'The International Dimension of Democratization and Human Rights in Latin America'] EL/KS UNU paper, 6/00, 2000; MS177.010.015.00013 (Box 15)
  - [2001: 'The International Dimension of Democratization and Human Rights in Latin America'] EL/KS UNU article, 2000; MS177.010.015.00014 (Box 15)
  - Misc. notes re: HR trials, 2000; MS177.010.015.00015 (Box 15)
  - Universal jurisdiction - misc., 1999; MS177.010.015.00016 (Box 15)
  - Astiz, 1982 -- 2000; MS177.010.015.00017 (Box 15)
  - Miguel Cavallo - Mexico / Argentina, 2000; MS177.010.015.00018 (Box 15)
  - Suarez Mason judgements, AI brief, 1988 -- 2000; MS177.010.015.00019 (Box 15)
  - Italian case against Suarez Mason, et al., 2000; MS177.010.015.00020 (Box 15)
  - Jorge Olivero, 2000; MS177.010.015.00021 (Box 15)
  - Argentina: PRATS case, 2000; MS177.010.015.00022 (Box 15)
  - DeNegri, 1988 -- 1992; MS177.010.015.00023 (Box 15)
  - Iturriaga extradition to Italy (Chile), 2000; MS177.010.015.00024 (Box 15)
  - Larios (Chile), 2000; MS177.010.015.00025 (Box 15)
  - Letelier v. Rep. of Chile, 1995 -- 2000; MS177.010.015.00026 (Box 15)
  - El Salvador case - US, 2000; MS177.010.015.00027 (Box 15)
  - Guatemalan cases in Spanish cts, 2000; MS177.010.015.00028 (Box 15)
  - Haiti: Raboteau trial, 2000; MS177.010.015.00029 (Box 15)
  - Evans Paul v. Prosper Avril [1 of 2], 1991 -- 1994; MS177.010.015.00030 (Box 15)
  - Evans Paul v. Prosper Avril [2 of 2], 1991; MS177.010.015.00031 (Box 15)
  - Gramajo [1 of 2], 1993 -- 1995; MS177.010.015.00032 (Box 15)
  - Gramajo [2of 2], 1995; MS177.010.015.00033 (Box 15)
  - Dutch ct. case re" Suriname, 2000; MS177.010.015.00034 (Box 15)
  - Khmer Rouge, 2000; MS177.010.015.00035 (Box 15)
  - Congo, 2000; MS177.010.015.00036 (Box 15)
  - Guinto v. Marcos, 1986; MS177.010.015.00037 (Box 15)
  - Filartiga v. Peña [1 of 2], 1984; MS177.010.015.00038 (Box 15)
  - Filartiga v. Peña [2 of 2], 1977 -- 1984; MS177.010.015.00039 (Box 15)
  - Ex Parte Quirin, 1942; MS177.010.015.00040 (Box 15)
  - In re Yamashita, 1946; MS177.010.015.00041 (Box 15)
  - [2001: 'The Justice Cascade: The Evolution and Impact of Foreign Human Rights Trials in Latin America'] The Justice Cascade EL/KS, 1/01, MS177.010.015.00042 (Box 15)
  - [2001: 'The Justice Cascade: The Evolution and Impact of Foreign Human Rights Trials in Latin America'] Chicago Journal Int'l Law article, MS177.010.015.00043 (Box 15)
  - Brown U (Carnegie) talk, 6/02, 2002; MS177.010.015.00045 (Box 15)
  - Sri Lanka meeting, 2002; MS177.010.015.00046 (Box 15)
  - [Imagine Coexistence: Findings and Recommendations for UNHCR], 2002; MS177.010.015.00047 (Box 15)
  - [Resolving rights conflicts notebook], 2002; MS177.010.015.00048 (Box 15)
  - H.R. clinicals conference, 2002; MS177.010.015.00049 (Box 15)
  - Colombia talk KSG, 5/02, ICG Colombia seminar, Wash. D.C. 6/02, 2002; MS177.010.015.00050 (Box 15)
  - Pinochet / Bush admin / Justice op ed, 2001; MS177.010.015.00051 (Box 15)
  - Tony Pereira syllabus re: justice and democracy in Latin America, 2001; MS177.010.015.00052 (Box 15)
  - Resolving rights conflicts, 2002; MS177.010.015.00053 (Box 15)
  - ICL lecture in Johnston's International Organization class - 11/02, 2002; MS177.010.015.00054 (Box 15)
  - Northern Ireland conference / Paper, 2002; MS177.010.015.00055 (Box 15)
  - ICTY at 10, 2002; MS177.010.015.00056 (Box 15)
  - ACR-NE 2002 conf., MS177.010.015.00057 (Box 15)
  - The Case Against Henry Kissinger, Christopher Hitchens, 2002; MS177.010.015.00058 (Box 15)
  - [2002: 'Troubleshooting Differences'] Paper for Carnegie, MS177.010.016.00001 (Box 16)
  - [2002: 'The Cavallo Case and the Future of Universal Jurisdiction'] Cavallo article, 2001 -- 2002; MS177.010.016.00002 (Box 16)
  - [2002: 'The Cavallo Case and the Future of Universal Jurisdiction'] Cavallo, 2001; MS177.010.016.00003 (Box 16)
  - Scenario planning, 2002; MS177.010.016.00004 (Box 16)
  - Cavallo, 2001; MS177.010.016.00005 (Box 16)
  - Roelf Mayer talk 3/3/03, 2003; MS177.010.016.00006 (Box 16)
  - [Lecture on justice sector], 2003; MS177.010.016.00007 (Box 16)
  - Al Rubin conference papers, ethics and authority in international law, 2003; MS177.010.016.00008 (Box 16)
  - EL paper: Wither Universal Jurisdiction (Al Rubin conf.), 2003; MS177.010.016.00009 (Box 16)
  - Human rights in the Americas 2003 talk, MS177.010.016.00010 (Box 16)
  - Belfast conference, HR/CR Network, 2003; MS177.010.016.00011 (Box 16)
  - [Photographs from Belfast], 2003; MS177.010.016.00012 (Box 16)
  - Universal jurisdiction / HOS Rubin Festshrift art., 2003; MS177.010.016.00013 (Box 16)
  - Inter-American HR machinery, 2003; MS177.010.016.00014 (Box 16)
  - SSRC criminal accountability conference, 2003; MS177.010.016.00015 (Box 16)
    Social Science Research Council Workshop on International Criminal Accountability
  - [Literature regarding peace negotiations and NGOs], 1997 -- 2001; MS177.010.016.00016 (Box 16)
  - Report of Secretary General on UN work - 2000, MS177.010.016.00017 (Box 16)
  - Secretary General Report on Protection of Civilians in Armed Conflict (2001), MS177.010.016.00018 (Box 16)
  - [United Nations Security Council 4109th meeting], 2000; MS177.010.016.00019 (Box 16)
  - Reports re: genocide in Rwanda - UN, OAU, 1999 -- 2000; MS177.010.016.00020 (Box 16)
  - Rule of law, 1991 -- 2003; MS177.010.016.00021 (Box 16)
  - World Bank Involvement in Post-Conflict Reconstruction, 1997; MS177.010.016.00022 (Box 16)
  - 'We the People's' millenium report of Secretary General / GA Dec., 2000; MS177.010.016.00023 (Box 16)
  - [Literature regarding human rights and conflict management], 2002; MS177.010.016.00024 (Box 16)
  - Brahimi report and Secretary General's response, Secretary Council response - 2000, MS177.010.016.00025 (Box 16)
  - [Boston Consortium], 2003; MS177.010.016.00026 (Box 16)
  - [2003] The Cavallo Case: One Year Later (aritcle for ACLU), MS177.010.016.00027 (Box 16)
  - Materials in preparation of frameworks document [1 of 2], 2001; MS177.010.016.00029 (Box 16)
  - Materials in preparation of frameworks document [2 of 2], 2001; MS177.010.016.00030 (Box 16)
  - U.S.I.P. articles, 2001; MS177.010.016.00031 (Box 16)
    United States Institute of Peace
  - Frameworks document, 2001 -- 2002; MS177.010.016.00032 (Box 16)
  - [Literature regarding human rights, peacekeeping and conflict resolution], 1998 -- 2001; MS177.010.016.00033 (Box 16)
  - [Literature regarding human rights, peacekeeping and conflict resolution], 1998 -- 2003; MS177.010.016.00034 (Box 16)
  - HR/CR - A gender-based perspective, 2004; MS177.010.016.00035 (Box 16)
  - NYT torture letter, 2004; MS177.010.016.00036 (Box 16)
  - GCSP - Geneva trip 11/04, 2004; MS177.010.016.00037 (Box 16)
  - Women in armed conflict, 2005; MS177.010.016.00038 (Box 16)
  - Women's rights I [1 of 3], 1996 -- 2004; MS177.010.016.00039 (Box 16)
  - Women's rights I [2 of 3], 1990 -- 1997; MS177.010.017.00001 (Box 17)
  - Women's rights I [3 of 3], 1996 -- 1997; MS177.010.017.00002 (Box 17)
  - Spring 05 - Cornell U. talks, 2005; MS177.010.017.00003 (Box 17)
  - [2006: 'Transitional Justice: Lessons Learned and the Road Ahead,' outline and literature], 1993 -- 2005; MS177.010.017.00005 (Box 17)
  - Transitional justice project, 2001; MS177.010.017.00006 (Box 17)
  - [Literature regarding accountability, ICC and transitional justice], 2001 -- 2004; MS177.010.017.00007 (Box 17)
  - Sierra Leone, 2003 -- 2004; MS177.010.017.00008 (Box 17)
  - Proposal to International Center for Transitional Justice, 2005; MS177.010.017.00009 (Box 17)
  - [2006: 'Transitional Justice: Lessons Learned and the Road Ahead,' correspondence], 2004; MS177.010.017.00010 (Box 17)
  - Naomi's book, 2004; MS177.010.017.00011 (Box 17)
  - [2006: 'Transitional Justice: Lessons Learned and the Road Ahead,' drafts and other Transitional Justice chapters, 1 of 5], 2004; MS177.010.017.00012 (Box 17)
  - [2006: 'Transitional Justice: Lessons Learned and the Road Ahead,' drafts and other Transitional Justice chapters, 2 of 5], 2004 -- 2005; MS177.010.017.00013 (Box 17)
  - [2006: 'Transitional Justice: Lessons Learned and the Road Ahead,' drafts and other Transitional Justice chapters, 3 of 5], 2004 -- 2005; MS177.010.017.00014 (Box 17)
  - [2006: 'Transitional Justice: Lessons Learned and the Road Ahead,' drafts and other Transitional Justice chapters, 4 of 5], 2004 -- 2005; MS177.010.017.00015 (Box 17)
  - [2006: 'Transitional Justice: Lessons Learned and the Road Ahead,' drafts and other Transitional Justice chapters, 5 of 5], 2004 -- 2005; MS177.010.017.00016 (Box 17)
  - [2006: 'Commentary: International Criminal Accountability at the Intersection of Law and Politics'] articles for Chandra book, 2005; MS177.010.017.00017 (Box 17)
  - Center of HR in Conflict, Chandra Sriram's group, 2005; MS177.010.017.00018 (Box 17)
  - [2006: 'Understanding Human Rights Violations in Contemporary Armed Conflict'] USIP - Understanding Rights Violations in Armed Conflict, 2003; MS177.010.017.00019 (Box 17)
  - [2006: 'Understanding Human Rights Violations in Contemporary Armed Conflict'] USIP book article, 2003 -- 2006; MS177.010.017.00020 (Box 17)
  - [2006: 'Understanding Human Rights Violations in Contemporary Armed Conflict'] USIP HR and Conflict book, EL article, 2005; MS177.010.017.00021 (Box 17)
  - [2006: 'Understanding Human Rights Violations in Contemporary Armed Conflict'], 2003 -- 2006; MS177.010.017.00022 (Box 17)
  - U. Wisconsin transitional justice conference - 4/19-20/2007, MS177.010.017.00023 (Box 17)
  - [2009: Prosecuting Heads of State, correspondence and notes], 2005; MS177.010.017.00024 (Box 17)
  - [2009: Prosecuting Heads of State, overview] Trying Heads of State, 2001; MS177.010.017.00025 (Box 17)
  - [2009: Prosecuting Heads of State] USIP grant, Trying Heads of State, 2003; MS177.010.017.00026 (Box 17)
  - [2009: Prosecuting Heads of State, Cambridge University Press and reviews], 2007; MS177.010.017.00027 (Box 17)
  - [2009: Prosecuting Heads of State] USIP grant proposal, 2004 -- 2008; MS177.010.017.00028 (Box 17)
  - [2009: Prosecuting Heads of State, notebook], 2006; MS177.010.018.00001 (Box 18)
  - Carlos the Jackel - terrorist, Jacques Verges - atty., 1994; MS177.010.018.00002 (Box 18)
  - [2009: Prosecuting Heads of State, country chart and correspondence], 2008; MS177.010.018.00003 (Box 18)
  - Aryeh Neier interview 1/4/08, 2008; MS177.010.018.00004 (Box 18)
  - [2009] Prosecuting Heads of State, reviews comments, 2008; MS177.010.018.00005 (Box 18)
  - [2009: Prosecuting Heads of State, articles], 2008; MS177.010.018.00006 (Box 18)
  - Milosevic, 2007; MS177.010.018.00007 (Box 18)
  - [2009: Prosecuting Heads of State, country charts and articles], 2005 -- 2008; MS177.010.018.00008 (Box 18)
  - [2009: Prosecuting Heads of State, Europe research files] Category 1: Soviet era: Romania, Ceausescu, 1989 -- 2002; MS177.010.018.00009 (Box 18)
  - [2009: Prosecuting Heads of State, Europe research files] Category 1: Soviet era: Czech Republic, Lenart, 1992 -- 2004; MS177.010.018.00010 (Box 18)
  - [2009: Prosecuting Heads of State, Europe research files] Category 1: Soviet era [Bulgaria, Zhivkov], 1991 -- 2007; MS177.010.018.00011 (Box 18)
  - [2009: Prosecuting Heads of State, Europe research files] Category 2: Nazis, 2001 -- 2007; MS177.010.018.00012 (Box 18)
  - [2009: Prosecuting Heads of State, Europe research files] Category 2: Nazis: East Germany, Krenz, 1995 -- 2005; MS177.010.018.00013 (Box 18)
  - [2009: Prosecuting Heads of State, Europe research files] Category 2: Nazis: Austria, Waldheim, 2001 -- 2007; MS177.010.018.00014 (Box 18)
  - [2009: Prosecuting Heads of State, Europe research files] Category 2: Nazis: France, Papon, 1995 -- 2007; MS177.010.018.00015 (Box 18)
  - [2009: Prosecuting Heads of State, Europe research files] Category 3: Balkans [Bosnia and Herzegovina], 2004; MS177.010.018.00016 (Box 18)
  - [2009: Prosecuting Heads of State, Europe research files] Category 3: Balkans [Belarus, Chigir], 1999 -- 2007; MS177.010.018.00017 (Box 18)
  - [2009: Prosecuting Heads of State, Europe research files] Category 3: Balkans: Bosnia, Sarovic, 2003; MS177.010.018.00018 (Box 18)
  - [2009: Prosecuting Heads of State, Europe research files] Category 3: Balkans: Bosnia, Karadzic, 2000 -- 2007; MS177.010.018.00019 (Box 18)
  - [2009: Prosecuting Heads of State, Europe research files] Category 3: Balkans: Yugoslavia, Milosevic, 2005; MS177.010.018.00020 (Box 18)
  - [2009: Prosecuting Heads of State, Europe research files] Category 3: Contemporary, 2002; MS177.010.018.00021 (Box 18)
  - [2009: Prosecuting Heads of State, Europe research files] Category 3: Contemporary: Lithuania, Paksas, 2004; MS177.010.018.00022 (Box 18)
  - [2009: Prosecuting Heads of State, Europe research files] Category 3: Contemporary: Armenia, Kocharian, 2003 -- 2004; MS177.010.018.00023 (Box 18)
  - [2009: Prosecuting Heads of State, Europe research files] Category 3: Contemporary: Italy, Berlusconi, 2001 -- 2008; MS177.010.018.00024 (Box 18)
  - [2009: Prosecuting Heads of State, Europe research files] Category 3: Contemporary: Poland, Jaruzelski, 2001 -- 2008; MS177.010.018.00025 (Box 18)
  - [2009: Prosecuting Heads of State, Europe research files] Category 3: Contemporary: France, Chriac, 2001 -- 2005; MS177.010.018.00026 (Box 18)
  - [2009: Prosecuting Heads of State, Europe research files] Category 3: Contemporary: Albania, Alia, 1991 -- 2007; MS177.010.018.00027 (Box 18)
  - [2009: Prosecuting Heads of State, Europe research files] Category 3: Contemporary [Macedonia], 2003 -- 2004; MS177.010.018.00028 (Box 18)
  - [2009: Prosecuting Heads of State] Financial reports, 2005; MS177.010.018.00029 (Box 18)
  - [Literature regarding trials of heads of state], 2005; MS177.010.018.00030 (Box 18)
  - [2009: Prosecuting Heads of State] Trying Heads of State, Meeting of Prosecution Network and pre-publication authors, 2006; MS177.010.018.00031 (Box 18)
  - I.C.C., 2005 -- 2007; MS177.010.018.00032 (Box 18)
    International Criminal Court
  - Materials for chart preparation, 1999 -- 2003; MS177.010.018.00033 (Box 18)
  - M. Osiel articles, 2005 -- 2007; MS177.010.018.00034 (Box 18)
  - Sikkink and Wallerstein, 'Errors about Trials', 2006; MS177.010.018.00035 (Box 18)
  - Posner on political trials, 2005 -- 2006; MS177.010.018.00036 (Box 18)
  - [2009: Prosecuting Heads of State] Charts: past versions, 2005; MS177.010.018.00037 (Box 18)
  - Klaus Barbie, 1989 -- 1991; MS177.010.018.00038 (Box 18)
  - Chile, 2007; MS177.010.018.00039 (Box 18)
  - Costa Rica, 2007; MS177.010.018.00040 (Box 18)
  - Rios Montt / Guatemala, 2007; MS177.010.018.00041 (Box 18)
  - Haiti, 2007; MS177.010.018.00042 (Box 18)
  - Mexico, 2005 -- 2007; MS177.010.018.00043 (Box 18)
  - Nicaragua, 2007; MS177.010.018.00044 (Box 18)
  - Paraguay, 2006 -- 2007; MS177.010.018.00045 (Box 18)
  - Fujimori / Peru, 2005 -- 2007; MS177.010.018.00046 (Box 18)
  - Venezuela, 2007; MS177.010.018.00047 (Box 18)
  - Bordaberry - Uruguay, 2006 -- 2007; MS177.010.018.00048 (Box 18)
  - Almonacid Arellano v. Chile (amnesty's dead), 2006; MS177.010.018.00049 (Box 18)
  - Saddam Hussein, 2007; MS177.010.018.00050 (Box 18)
  - Taylor, 2005 -- 2007; MS177.010.018.00051 (Box 18)
  - East Timor, 2004 -- 2006; MS177.010.018.00052 (Box 18)
  - [2009: Prosecuting Heads of State, manuscript and notes, 1 of 3], 2008; MS177.010.018.00053 (Box 18)
  - [2009: Prosecuting Heads of State, manuscript and notes, 2 of 3], 2008; MS177.010.018.00054 (Box 18)
  - [2009: Prosecuting Heads of State, manuscript and notes, 3 of 3], 1996 -- 2007; MS177.010.018.00055 (Box 18)
  - Book correspondence, 2004; MS177.010.018.00056 (Box 18)
  - Argentina, 2005 -- 2007; MS177.010.018.00057 (Box 18)
  - Bolivia, 2007; MS177.010.018.00058 (Box 18)
  - Brazil, 2007; MS177.010.019.00001 (Box 19)
  - [2009: Prosecuting Heads of State] Table summaries and CD [Final draft], 2007; MS177.010.019.00002 (Box 19)
  - [2009: Prosecuting Heads of State] Table summaries and CD: Cameroon - Ahiojo, 1989; MS177.010.019.00003 (Box 19)
  - [2009: Prosecuting Heads of State] Table summaries and CD: Central African Republic - Bakassa, 1987 -- 2002; MS177.010.019.00004 (Box 19)
  - [2009: Prosecuting Heads of State] Table summaries and CD: Chad - Habre, 2000 -- 2007; MS177.010.019.00005 (Box 19)
  - [2009: Prosecuting Heads of State] Table summaries and CD: DR Congo - various, 1998 -- 2003; MS177.010.019.00006 (Box 19)
  - [2009: Prosecuting Heads of State] Table summaries and CD: South Africa - Botha, 1996 -- 2007; MS177.010.019.00007 (Box 19)
  - [2009: Prosecuting Heads of State] Table summaries and CD: Ethiopia - Mariam, 1979 -- 2007; MS177.010.019.00008 (Box 19)
  - [2009: Prosecuting Heads of State] Table summaries and CD: Liberia / Sierra Leone - Taylor, 2003 -- 2007; MS177.010.019.00009 (Box 19)
  - [2009: Prosecuting Heads of State] Table summaries and CD: Madagascar - Ratsiraka, 2003; MS177.010.019.00010 (Box 19)
  - [2009: Prosecuting Heads of State] Table summaries and CD: Malawi - Banda, 1995 -- 1997; MS177.010.019.00011 (Box 19)